<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Philip Broadway - Articles</title>
    <description>Application Design &amp; Development</description>
    <link>
    http://localhost:4000</link>
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Listabot Plus Size Update!</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.listabot.com&quot;&gt;Listabot&lt;/a&gt; v1.04 is live in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/listabot/id1212689677&quot;&gt;App Store&lt;/a&gt; now!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/listabot-update</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/listabot-update</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Project Planning</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;I suggest trying to break up all the tasks that make up your project into as many discrete “single serving” tasks as possible. The reason for doing this is simple.
We want to be able to measure &amp;amp; communicate progress for you and your client. Small tasks can be worked on or paused as needed.
This allows you to complete tasks in the order that makes sense for you, while still being able to see overall progress being made.
This is important data for you &amp;amp; for your client!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/project-planning</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/project-planning</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>ListaBot Launch</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I released my first public version of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.listabot.com&quot;&gt;Listabot&lt;/a&gt; in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/listabot/id1212689677&quot;&gt;App Store&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve contracted &amp;amp; freelanced on &amp;amp; off for many years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the course of those years I’ve used many different platforms for tracking billable hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most require an account to setup before you can even enter a task and actually get to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a small team environment, you might even end up assigning one person to just master the system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That sole person would then be responsible for assigning &amp;amp; maintaining the tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Taskmaster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s ironic that something used to track time, could actually end up wasting so much of your time. 
Your team’s time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Except that wasted time isn’t just a hassle - those are billable hours you’ve just lost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;assets/images/blog/listabot-v1.01/new-challenger.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Screen shot from Street Fighter of a new challenger appearing&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve made  &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.listabot.com&quot;&gt;Listabot&lt;/a&gt; to minimize the friction for simply tracking your billable hours spent on project tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The benefits for tracking your billable hours become apparent over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously, tracking your billable hours is important if you want to get paid for your work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But &lt;em&gt;how&lt;/em&gt; you track your time can also save time when you are making estimates for your next project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With your past performance accurately recorded &amp;amp; easy to analyze, you not only have a record to improve on, but a measuring stick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t just your invoice, this is your record to improve upon.
A tool for spotting pain-points &amp;amp; anticipated where more time will be spent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a roadmap of features I’m implementing incrementally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d like to begin adding these features &amp;amp; others as they are requested by users like &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My mission with this app will always be to keep billable hour tracking &lt;em&gt;simple &amp;amp; intuitive&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in learning about new features as they are released, please join the &lt;a href=&quot;http://eepurl.com/cKCi3n&quot;&gt;mailing list&lt;/a&gt; or just stay in touch on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/listabot&quot;&gt;Facebook page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/listabot-launch</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/listabot-launch</guid>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
